(Sheldon:)Oh.
Yeah, this little guy
(Sheldon:)can already recognize
(Sheldon:)electronically
transmitted images
(Sheldon:)20% faster than any other
sample in Amy's lab.
(Bernadette:)I'm running out of ways
to act excited.
(Amy:)So, enough about us,
how are things going with you?
(Bernadette:)Great, the doctor
said the baby's head
(Bernadette:)is facing down now.
(Amy:)Good, you know,
(Amy:)in case the exit
isn't clearly marked.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I have to say,
it is nice to share
(Sheldon:)this experience with someone
who's on the same journey.
(Sheldon:)Although right now ours
is testing off the charts
(Sheldon:)while yours is floating
around in its own waste.
(Bernadette:)Are you actually comparing
my human baby
(Bernadette:)to your brain in a bowl?
(Sheldon:)Well, I didn't
make you waddle up
(Sheldon:)four flights of stairs
for the heck of it.
(Bernadette:)You do realize my baby
has functioning organs
(Bernadette:)and can recognize voices.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, but ours can recognize
a specific data stream